( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Who's there?
من هناك؟
Nongyu,
نونجيو،
I saw your room light was on.
رأيت أن ضوء غرفتك كان مضاءً.
Is something wrong?
هل هناك خطب ما؟
I woke up suddenly.
استيقظت فجأة.
The room felt kind of strange.
كان الشعور في الغرفة غريباً نوعاً ما.
I'll take a look.
سألقي نظرة.
There's nothing.
لا يوجد شيء.
Maybe I was too worn out during the day.
ربما كنت منهكاً للغاية خلال النهار.
My nerves are on edge.
أعصابي متوترة للغاية.
I learned about
لقد تعلمت عن
a really effective massage technique.
تقنية تدليك فعالة للغاية.
Want to try it?
هل ترغب بتجربته؟
You can't offer that kind of service
لا يمكنك تقديم هذا النوع من الخدمة
to female friends who aren't your girlfriend.
إلى صديقاتك الإناث اللواتي لسن حبيباتك.
Call me if anything happens.
اتصل بي إذا حدث أي شيء.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
No.
لا.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
It's dangerous.
إنه أمر خطير.
Why didn't you grab him just now?
لماذا لم تمسك به الآن؟
No.
لا.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Chief Zhang,
الرئيس تشانغ،
we didn't find anyone here.
لم نجد أحداً هنا.
Keep searching.
استمر في البحث.
Roger that.
استلمت هذا.
By the time the squad got there yesterday, no one was left.
عندما وصل الفريق إلى هناك أمس، لم يكن هناك أحد متبقٍ.
The fragment was probably taken by Wu Nongyu.
من المحتمل أن يكون وو نونغيو قد أخذ القطعة.
Why is she pulling tricks again?
لماذا تلجأ إلى الحيل مجدداً؟
She's such a pain.
إنها مزعجة للغاية.
Dear,
عزيزي،
be careful not to cut your hand.
احرص على عدم جرح يدك.
Those two fragments Wu Siyuan brought back
تلك القطعتان اللتان أحضرهما وو سييوان
were probably fake.
ربما كانت مزيفة.
Otherwise, Wu Nongyu
وإلا، وو نونغيو
wouldn't need to look for this third fragment.
لن نحتاج للبحث عن هذا الجزء الثالث.
We got fooled by those siblings again.
لقد انخدعنا بهؤلاء الأشقاء مرة أخرى.
Besides Lin Juan,
إلى جانب لين جوان،
Xie Xinxu showed up too.
كما حضر شي شينكسو.
What's so great about Wu Nongyu?
ما الذي يميز وو نونغيو؟
Xie Xinxu is really bad at choosing partners.
شي شينكسو سيئة للغاية في اختيار الشركاء.
Send out
أرسل
all field agents
جميع العملاء الميدانيين
to find Wu Nongyu and Xie Xinxu.
للعثور على Wu Nongyu وXie Xinxu.
They must be found
يجب العثور عليهم
within two days.
في غضون يومين.
Mom,
أم،
maybe I could...
ربما أستطيع...
Forget about it.
انسَ الأمر.
You're good for nothing
أنت لا تصلح لشيء
except that pretty face.
باستثناء ذلك الوجه الجميل.
I'm done. No appetite.
انتهيت. لا شهية لي.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Mom,
أم،
I really don't want to
لا أريد ذلك حقاً
and I'm not willing to just waste my whole life at home like this.
وأنا لست مستعداً لإضاعة حياتي كلها في المنزل هكذا.
Lu,
الاثنين،
life isn't long.
الحياة ليست طويلة.
Whether you're happy with it or not,
سواء كنت راضياً عن ذلك أم لا،
you still live it.
ما زلت تعيشها.
Lu,
الاثنين،
in this family,
في هذه العائلة،
your main job is to take good care of Yan.
مهمتك الرئيسية هي الاعتناء جيداً بيان.
When you finally please her,
عندما تُرضيها أخيرًا،
then we can talk about other things.
ثم يمكننا التحدث عن أمور أخرى.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I need to find a place to develop the medicine.
أحتاج إلى إيجاد مكان لتطوير الدواء.
Time's tight.
الوقت ضيق.
The Special Administration Bureau must be looking for us.
لا بد أن مكتب الإدارة الخاصة يبحث عنا.
Let's go to Mr. Ding's place.
هيا بنا إلى منزل السيد دينغ.
His house is in the suburbs.
يقع منزله في الضواحي.
Very secluded.
منعزل للغاية.
He also
وهو أيضاً
has a private lab at home.
يمتلك مختبرًا خاصًا في المنزل.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
It'll be convenient.
سيكون ذلك مناسباً.
That sounds good.
فكرة جميلة.
Do you have any tissues?
هل لديك مناديل ورقية؟
In my bag.
في حقيبتي.
You used the blood-exchanging device to form a pact with me?
هل استخدمت جهاز تبادل الدم لعقد اتفاق معي؟
Isn't this used for exchanging viruses?
أليس هذا يُستخدم لتبادل الفيروسات؟
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Can't find it?
ألا تجده؟
No, I found it.
لا، لقد وجدته.
Why would he carry something for virus exchange around with him?
لماذا يحمل معه شيئاً لتبادل الفيروسات؟
[LZY]
[LZY]
Call me back.
اتصل بي لاحقاً.
Mr. Ding has gotten everything ready.
لقد جهز السيد دينغ كل شيء.
You two go in first.
ادخلا أنتما أولاً.
I have something to take care of.
لديّ أمرٌ عليّ القيام به.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Your information was accurate.
معلوماتك كانت دقيقة.
We've got the third fragment.
لقد حصلنا على الجزء الثالث.
Mom,
أم،
my people heard
سمع شعبي
the third fragment is likely in Xiaoshan Village.
من المرجح أن يكون الجزء الثالث في قرية شياوشان.
Should I go check it out?
هل يجب أن أذهب لألقي نظرة؟
It's dangerous over there.
الوضع هناك خطير.
I'll send someone else.
سأرسل شخصاً آخر.
Fine.
بخير.
She uses that excuse every time.
إنها تستخدم هذا العذر في كل مرة.
Can't you even dodge that?
ألا يمكنك حتى تفادي ذلك؟
Useless.
عديم الفائدة.
You make me lose my appetite.
أنت تجعلني أفقد شهيتي.
I have a lead on the third fragment.
لدي خيط يقودني إلى الجزء الثالث.
[LZY]
[LZY]
Let's make a deal.
لنعقد صفقة.
Xia Shang is searching for you everywhere.
شيا شانغ يبحث عنك في كل مكان.
Hide well.
مخبأ آمن.
Develop the medicine for me as soon as possible.
قم بتطوير الدواء لي في أسرع وقت ممكن.
I have to get away from that disgusting mother and daughter.
يجب أن أبتعد عن تلك الأم وابنتها المقرفتين.
I can't put up with them another day.
لا أستطيع تحملهم يوماً آخر.
That's a wrap for today!
هذا كل شيء لليوم!
Mr. Ding
السيد دينغ
logged all fragment data.
تم تسجيل جميع بيانات الأجزاء.
I've also finished the prep work.
لقد انتهيت أيضاً من أعمال التحضير.
We'll rest tonight
سنرتاح الليلة
and go full speed tomorrow.
وانطلق بأقصى سرعة غداً.
Well.
حسنًا.
This is going to be
سيكون هذا
a long night.
ليلة طويلة.
Hey.
يا.
Maybe we should get some supplements
ربما ينبغي أن نحصل على بعض المكملات الغذائية
to replenish ourselves properly.
لنعيد ملء أنفسنا بشكل صحيح.
Oh right.
أوه صحيح.
Find me some virus-suppressing medicine.
ابحث لي عن دواء لكبح الفيروسات.
My brain
دماغي
is overworked.
إنه مثقل بالأعباء.
I'm feeling under the weather now.
أشعر بتوعك الآن.
Virus-suppressing medicine?
دواء مثبط للفيروسات؟
Oh, right.
أوه، صحيح.
I'll get it for you right away.
سأحضره لك على الفور.
She's finished the injection
لقد انتهت من الحقنة
and fallen asleep.
وغطّ في النوم.
It's only been one day,
لقد مر يوم واحد فقط،
and the virus flared up again.
ثم انتشر الفيروس مجدداً.
Is your blood even working?
هل تعمل دمتك بشكل صحيح؟
The virus will soon be gone.
سيختفي الفيروس قريباً.
When that time comes,
عندما يحين ذلك الوقت،
my blood won't work anymore.
لم يعد دمي يعمل.
After everything is over,
بعد انتهاء كل شيء،
I won't let you get close to her again.
لن أسمح لك بالاقتراب منها مرة أخرى.
I knew it. Lin Juan and you teamed up to lie to me.
كنت أعرف ذلك. لقد تعاونت أنت ولين جوان للكذب عليّ.
There was never any medicine, right?
لم يكن هناك أي دواء على الإطلاق، أليس كذلك؟
These past two years,
خلال العامين الماضيين،
you've been secretly coming to exchange the virus with me.
لقد كنت تأتي سراً لتبادل الفيروس معي.
I saw the device.
لقد رأيت الجهاز.
Yes.
نعم.
What you were given were just regular nutrient injections
ما تم إعطاؤه لك كان مجرد حقن مغذية عادية
with a bit of sedative.
مع القليل من المهدئات.
No wonder
لا عجب
I always slept so deeply
كنت أنام دائمًا نومًا عميقًا جدًا
after the injections
بعد الحقن
and had a hard time waking up the next day.
وواجه صعوبة في الاستيقاظ في اليوم التالي.
Was Lin Juan your accomplice?
هل كان لين جوان شريكك؟
Why didn't you tell me the truth from the start?
لماذا لم تخبرني الحقيقة منذ البداية؟
Meeting regularly to exchange the virus wouldn't have been that troublesome.
لم يكن الاجتماع بانتظام لتبادل المعلومات حول الفيروس أمراً صعباً للغاية.
I...
أنا...
I was afraid I would remind you
كنت أخشى أن أذكرك
of unhappy things.
من الأشياء التعيسة.
And look at you with disgust?
وأنظر إليك باشمئزاز؟
When I think about everything you've done for me
عندما أفكر في كل ما فعلته من أجلي
and how humble you still act,
وكم ما زلت تتصرف بتواضع!
I just feel like you've carried so much
أشعر وكأنك تحملت الكثير
for my sake.
من أجلي.
As the one benefiting from it all,
بصفتي المستفيد من كل ذلك،
it's hard not to feel guilty.
من الصعب ألا تشعر بالذنب.
No.
لا.
I wanted to do it this way.
أردت أن أفعل ذلك بهذه الطريقة.
You don't need to feel guilty.
لا داعي للشعور بالذنب.
You still love me very much,
ما زلت تحبني كثيراً،
right?
يمين؟
An unequal love
حب غير متكافئ
tends to make people feel pressured.
يميل ذلك إلى جعل الناس يشعرون بالضغط.
Being too domineering isn't good.
إن التسلط المفرط ليس بالأمر الجيد.
Being too humble isn't either.
التواضع المفرط ليس كذلك أيضاً.
So,
لذا،
from now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
don't suppress your true thoughts and feelings in front of me.
لا تكبت أفكارك ومشاعرك الحقيقية أمامي.
Love me more openly,
أحبني بشكل أكثر انفتاحاً،
okay?
تمام؟
Okay.
تمام.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪